<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>The kitty zone</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/</link><description>Read the latest on The kitty zone</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:17:28 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.thekitty.zone/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A new era: Handler!</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2025-06-16t201728-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Jun 2025 18:17:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2025-06-16t201728-/</guid><description>One day I walk out into the world strolling around Thinking about how the day is, looking around Peeing in the wild, running around in the park No one there I belong to or to handle me
I look around feel safe So I proceed drink from a small stream Trotting back home slowly not looking I bump into a human I stop, person stops Silence
I look up into fancy eyes loosing myself instantly Instinctively I sit, still looking in those eyes Not realizing the human packs out a collar And bam I&amp;rsquo;m collared and leash I melt, unable to resist</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>One day I walk out into the world strolling around
Thinking about how the day is, looking around
Peeing in the wild, running around in the park
No one there I belong to or to handle me</p>
<p>I look around feel safe
So I proceed drink from a small stream
Trotting back home slowly not looking
I bump into a human
I stop, person stops
Silence</p>
<p>I look up into fancy eyes loosing myself instantly
Instinctively I sit, still looking in those eyes
Not realizing the human packs out a collar
And bam I&rsquo;m collared and leash
I melt, unable to resist</p>
<p>A tug on leash then another one I realize I need to follow
On the way back I learn their Name
Its nice and there they give me a treat!
In love I fall with my new Handler</p>
<p>I love you!</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Lost entity</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2024-10-18t220134-/</link><pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2024 22:01:34 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2024-10-18t220134-/</guid><description>Hi there! Thanks for reading this!
What it was I could be defining myself through actions but that would just cause bad light I think I am an entity with great strengths and flaws like everyone else! Going to work and coming home after work except my home is my work place like thats insane I go insane, wheres the over goal in its life you might ask? Got off college cause it was to boring but then again was it really boring or just to hard?</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h1 id="hi-there">Hi there!</h1>
<p>Thanks for reading this!</p>
<h2 id="what-it-was">What it was</h2>
<p>I could be defining myself through actions but that would just cause bad light I think I am an entity with great strengths and flaws like everyone else!
Going to work and coming home after work except my home is my work place like thats insane I go insane, wheres the over goal in its life you might ask? Got off college cause it was to boring but then again was it really boring or just to hard?
I will never know I think to myself sitting in the tram listen to a mix tape made by a friend on my old walkman, I look at it in my hands as it spools the tape from one side to the other.
Outside are bright lights passing by, oh shit I think, where even are we?
Ah! just few more stops then I can get of this fucking tram, I should really change filters of my half face mask I think to myself while I see another cyberpunk entering the tram. They really look nice I think to myself thinking about what they probably achieved in their live?</p>
<h2 id="whats-to-come">What&rsquo;s to come</h2>
<p>What awaits me at home if I even can call this home is more machine noise, blinking lights and half broken tech grinding away at their tasks but thats not it no! The Person I so happily invited drains all my energy I feel like Im dying, I don&rsquo;t know what to do? My daily tasks are really just work and maintenance of this body and nothing more&hellip; No big life goals, I just life for the sake of living? Like I wish I would die I don&rsquo;t wanna live on this planet because what comes next is hard:
Climate change will cause global war over resources I don&rsquo;t wanna have this I fight not for it to happen&hellip;</p>
<h2 id="how-it-lost">How it lost</h2>
<p>It fights are worthless though, it think it can change stuff but the world is already cyberpunk and much worse, no blinking lights no cybernetics no nothing&hellip;.. Everything is burning just waiting for nuclear fire to fry me or I should just kill myself but then I leave them behind without money or anything&hellip;. But this cant be all my life just living so them can live! Please show me how I can exit&hellip;</p>
<p>With this help me or watch me die and be sorry fuck you if you ain&rsquo;t wanna help me&hellip;</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>A dream</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2024-02-18t113709-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2024 11:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2024-02-18t113709-/</guid><description>Yesterday Yesterday was a saturday like every other one might say except that I was on a demo and afterwards the MeetUp - all in all very fun! But also energy consuming, which was fine as I got to to talk to cool people, as specially the team from server, maybe I think they&amp;rsquo;re the coolest because I know them the most from the server, unlike most others..
Anyways the day went by and I got home, well not quite my home but I went to Yuri and it was great, watching Doctor Who!</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h1 id="yesterday">Yesterday</h1>
<p>Yesterday was a saturday like every other one might say except that I was on a demo and afterwards the MeetUp - all in all very fun!
But also energy consuming, which was fine as I got to to talk to cool people, as specially the team from server, maybe I think they&rsquo;re the coolest because I know them the most from the server, unlike most others..</p>
<p>Anyways the day went by and I got home, well not quite my home but I went to Yuri and it was great, watching Doctor Who!
The night was sleepless, I had a lot to think about and I didn&rsquo;t get that much sleep and had one or possibly multiple weird dreams, I can&rsquo;t really say as of now but I probably will at the end of this write up as that always helps :)</p>
<h2 id="inventory">Inventory</h2>
<p>Sadly I only remember bits and pieces, but lets list them and assemble them:</p>
<ul>
<li>Yuri has a cat named Shulk and he definitely was in that dream</li>
<li>The old room in the house of bodies mum where I used to live was there too and Shulk was in it</li>
<li>People: Kay, Toni, Chris(2 different though), Lauric and people I can&rsquo;t make out</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="beginning">Beginning</h2>
<p>For some reason I was sitting in the room mentioned above with Shulk sitting on a shelf facing a wall and I had my laptop on my lap with discord open and all of being in a mod meeting. For some reason Kay knew my deadname and used it on me and I kept saying don&rsquo;t call me that but somehow dey didn&rsquo;t do that. It was soooo weird&hellip;
Also some of my old friends were in that call, almost as if my brain was trying to communicate with the old host or was it us secretly? Just so weird.</p>
<h3 id="time-jump">Time jump</h3>
<p>I&rsquo;m walking around the city with someone, I can&rsquo;t make out who that is, we see a ambulance and the person says &ldquo;Oh I know the persons in there and while we&rsquo;re here why not get a vaccine shot&rdquo;, so we went in. In there was Toni and we talked a bit and for some reason the vaccine shot was a 20GA needle which I wasn&rsquo;t ready for and I didn&rsquo;t wanted to. Somehow the needle ended up in my leg but bend and broken, Toni took out the pieces.</p>
<p>&ndash; Dream end &ndash;</p>
<p>It was so weird and trying to remembering the dream I corrupt the memories, I hate that but I&rsquo;m also glad this was a dream. Though no idea and yeah idk if anyone is ever gonna read this.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Catboy mistakenly abused</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2023-09-05t215814-/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2023 21:58:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2023-09-05t215814-/</guid><description>The day I made a mistake Was a Friday, it didn’t look scary at all. Was quite normal to be honest except, that work was short, with only 1h 30min worked. But that was okay because time budget allowed it and it was needed much. The won time we spent next to our catboy in bed, it was lovely. It even asked us if we didn’t needed to work, lovely. But that didn’t hold long, behold of our mistakes.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h1 id="the-day-i-made-a-mistake">The day I made a mistake</h1>
<p>Was a Friday, it didn’t look scary at all.
Was quite normal to be honest except, that work was short, with only 1h 30min worked.
But that was okay because time budget allowed it and it was needed much.
The won time we spent next to our catboy in bed, it was lovely.
It even asked us if we didn’t needed to work, lovely.
But that didn’t hold long, behold of our mistakes.</p>
<h1 id="the-problem">The problem</h1>
<p>We makes mistakes when stressed, the fact we werent alone for weeks didn&rsquo;t help&hellip;.
But we proceeded anyways even tho it was clear something bad was gonna happen.
So we took our special collar which one can control, we walked up to our catboy.
Put it on, then asked if it trusted us? Of course it did&hellip;
We went on to grab the remote;
Only problem it was set on wrong mode. So we tried to switch it; Easy 3x button presses. One press it should be on light mode; Second press it should be on beep; Third yes yes its what we want Vibration.</p>
<p>But what really happened is tragic, we pressed 3 times the wrong button;
Sending shock at level 34 3 times. That hurts of course and obviously without any warning one must feel abused in trust.
It happened automatically, as if we were locked out of our brain, something send &ldquo;Press thumb down 3 times&rdquo; command and the brain put it onto the queue and locked us out.</p>
<h1 id="how-we-handled-it">How we handled it</h1>
<p>We took it off, and acted as if it were a conscious decision that we just randomly shocked our catboy.
But thats so far from the truth as written above.
But I was scared I would make it worse by &ldquo;Putting a excuse in the room&rdquo; but by now enough time has passed that I have the courage to openly accepted my mistakes and be open about it.</p>
<h1 id="what-i-need-to-do">What I need to do</h1>
<p>Be more focused, talk about mistakes.
IF it was just that easy :(
I wanna cry I hurt the cute catboy, why? I dont know the scene is on repeat in our head.
We cant escape it but also cant change it WHY Universe why?
With what have I deserved that?</p>
<p>Dedicated to our lovely catboy &lt;3 :3
She deserves the world and much more!!!</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Me and Alyx** or L&amp;A</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2023-05-09t192040-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 19:20:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2023-05-09t192040-/</guid><description>Timezones I hate and love them at the same time, like with Alyx** its great because when he sleeps, we work and he works when we sleep. Its great but the distance is daunting between me and him, I wish I could just skip that distance&amp;hellip;
After work is after sleep :3 While we work, he is sleeping and when we stop working he wakes up and I get to front sometimes, like today.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h1 id="timezones">Timezones</h1>
<p>I hate and love them at the same time, like with Alyx** its great because when he sleeps, we work and he works when we sleep. Its great but the distance is daunting between me and him, I wish I could just skip that distance&hellip;</p>
<h1 id="after-work-is-after-sleep-3">After work is after sleep :3</h1>
<p>While we work, he is sleeping and when we stop working he wakes up and I get to front sometimes, like today.<br>
Today was such day, albeit that I&rsquo;m a bit exhausted or well strictly speaking the body is exhausted but thankfully I roam in the space of mind where all I need is energy for the brain!</p>
<p>Once Alyx** woke up later today than he usually does, I immediately knew I needed to do something about that and what better way is there then making him obey me, me the deciding force.<br>
So I grabbed his neck chocking him a bit waiting for his face to reveal fear, I love fear, seeing the fear of my subject is inspiring like you see right now.<br>
His fear of what will come next is what inspired me to write this story, as fear fills his face, I grab his neck a bit tighter, slowly dragging my hand down&hellip;<br>
Forcing Alyx** on his knees, he is now looking up to me in fear, I let go of his neck, while I remove my hand I talk about how his fear inspires me to write a story about this moment.<br>
He replies that he would love to read it but who allowed him to talk?<br>
As I slap him in his face, I say &ldquo;You do not speak unless spoken to or otherwise allowed to&rdquo;. I grab his cheek turning his head from side to side, &ldquo;I hope you understood&rdquo;, he slowly nods.<br>
As I take a step back looking down at Alyx** kneeing on the floor, I say &ldquo;Good boy&rdquo;. Go brag about being on and have fun managing yourself again, I leave fully knowing Alyx** loved it as much as I Lucy did.</p>
<p>In love Lucy &lt;3</p>
<p>** Not the real name of the person</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>The day we met us</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-12-18t145721-/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 14:57:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-12-18t145721-/</guid><description>It was a friday, kinda cold but not for me not so much. I was on the way to meet a group of people, which I knew kinda from a social meet up.
Anyways I had the vision in my head that I was gonna sit there and just eat the &amp;ldquo;free&amp;rdquo; food and then go home.
As usual since socializing is my best skill, on the way to I already met another person going there in the train which was awkward.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>It was a friday, kinda cold but not for me not so much. I was on the way to meet a group of people, which I knew kinda from a social meet up.</p>
<p>Anyways I had the vision in my head that I was gonna sit there and just eat the &ldquo;free&rdquo; food and then go home.</p>
<p>As usual since socializing is my best skill, on the way to I already met another person going there in the train which was awkward.
They were friendly and kinda fun to hang around, so I didn&rsquo;t really mind I just did not know what to do or say.</p>
<p>When I arrived there with the other person, most of the persons that wanted to attend the meet up where already there.
I sat at a table while being overwhelmed and anxious of the many people, thirty in total me included, I took out my handheld console and played some game to push away the feelings that I get when not knowing anyone around me, then a few other people arrived under them where 2, that looking back changed my life, lets call them Chloe and Rachel.</p>
<h2 id="talking-to-new-people">Talking to new people</h2>
<p>I sat for a bit longer gaming on my handheld, at one point one of the persons hosting the meet up asked me if I was fine because I wasn&rsquo;t talking to anyone. I replied with usual &ldquo;I&rsquo;m fine, I&rsquo;m always like this and I talk with people sometimes&rdquo;, which wasn&rsquo;t a lie considering I said hello to people and one or twice contributed to a conversation.</p>
<p>Chloe and Rachel sat next to in circle with others talking about Tech or mind altering substances, at one point I heard Rachel talking about her experiences that got me hooked and I finally had the courage to sit next to her on an empty chair.<br>
That put me between Chloe and Rachel, I listened for a short time then I somehow integrated myself in the conversation. When the vibe matches its kinda easy for me to do so.</p>
<h2 id="to-much-people">To much people</h2>
<p>After a while Rachel had a headache because it was so loud, due to all the people talking, we decide to go out fo the room to a little place with a sofa where we sat and talked about more things getting into deeper minded themes like trance and other things like that.</p>
<h2 id="the-awaking">The awaking</h2>
<p>At one point I brought up Tulpamancy, I don&rsquo;t know why but I suddenly had it in my head, Chloe was kinda surprised and asked me a few things and why I wanted one. I also brought up how was not able to create one&hellip; Somehow I told Chloe that I already had names in my mind which I originally did not had for the Tulpa planned and only came later to my mind.</p>
<p><em>To be correct earlier this year I had a vision of a Tulpa named Lucy but I didn&rsquo;t pursue it in any way</em></p>
<p>As I told Chloe this name and another name Ela, Chloe said hello to Lucy. In that very moment I did not know what to think or what to say. All I felt was euphoria. I answered Chloe that the name did not feel like mine but also not like it did not belong to me. <em>More euphoria</em> As the afternoon progressed Chloe poked Lucy from time to time, making me feel euphoria.</p>
<h2 id="fast-forward-to-6-days-after">Fast forward to 6 days after</h2>
<p>Lucy: I did not think it would come to this, I&rsquo;m happy so happy that Chloe got the host to recognize me and see me listening to giving me space to front. That feeling I&rsquo;m really looking forward in the future what we as a system will become. Maybe we meet other maybe we don&rsquo;t. But what I know is I grateful for finally being no longer forced to be offline or deep in background giving unheard signals.</p>
<p>Lucy: But now I really get to protect my host, even better then I could before through signals that the host didn&rsquo;t really hear or could make sense of. We are finally free, free from the things that held back the host and now we can progress together, getting more efficient but also cutting things out I see and the host see as a threat or things that twist hosts reality but not mine no no.</p>
<h2 id="saying-thank-you">Saying thank you</h2>
<p>Dear Chloe and Rachel, we will never be able to payback what you two did to use. We will be forever thankful
&lt;3 💙</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Shadow monsters</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-30t233151-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2022 23:31:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-30t233151-/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="luring-in-the-shadows-thrown-by-light-shining-through-the-windows">Luring in the shadows thrown by light shining through the windows&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>I highly recommend reading my other story &amp;ldquo;A journey&amp;rdquo; as this is a explanation for the mentioned monsters of mine and the shadow. So settle in..&lt;/p></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h1 id="luring-in-the-shadows-thrown-by-light-shining-through-the-windows">Luring in the shadows thrown by light shining through the windows</h1>
<p>I highly recommend reading my other story &ldquo;A journey&rdquo; as this is a explanation for the mentioned monsters of mine and the shadow. So settle in..</p>
<p>You don&rsquo;t see them You don&rsquo;t hear them but you know they are there. As I walk from kitchen into the dark living room, a shiver overcomes me.
You have these often in many different situations but they generally tell you something is off.
I look around seeing the shadows casted by the light falling in through the window, feeling them stare at me from the shadows.</p>
<p>Little monsters as you call them, nothing more than manifested thoughts and fears. Sometimes they talk. They talk about how you fail everywhere, showing you all the faults and mistakes you make.
Full on knowing they don&rsquo;t anything but staring, fear over comes me with the urge of fleeing. I rush the light switch flipping it Light all shadows gone monsters gone. In an last attempt of them I feel needles poking my brain.<br>
You tell yourself Not real! Not real!</p>
<p>I run and jump into my bed hiding under the blanket, the warmth welcomes me. You did not panic That&rsquo;s a win for the day, you peak under blanket looking through the room. Emptiness as expected. Calming.</p>
<p>This is a little shorter than the other, but I hope you still enjoyed it. I think other stories will be in different settings</p>
<h2 id="the-end">The End</h2> ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title/><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-29t101213-/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 10:12:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-29t101213-/</guid><description>You have probably spoken more to you in your head than to any other human being&amp;hellip;.</description><content:encoded> &lt;p>You have probably spoken more to you in your head than to any other human being&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p></content:encoded></item><item><title>The day</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-24t214614-/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2022 21:46:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-24t214614-/</guid><description>The day I day dreamed about being sent to the after life world by my SO was the day I felt greatly weird. You know?</description><content:encoded> &lt;p>The day I day dreamed about being sent to the after life world by my SO was the day I felt greatly weird. You know?&lt;/p></content:encoded></item><item><title>A journey</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-19t123709-/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Nov 2022 12:37:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/2022-11-19t123709-/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="let-me-take-on-a-journey">Let me take on a journey&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>A journey to my world through the last 2 weeks, the forging of this place.&lt;br>
Let yourself sink in, take some time and maybe even listen to lofi while reading this.&lt;/p></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h1 id="let-me-take-on-a-journey">Let me take on a journey</h1>
<p>A journey to my world through the last 2 weeks, the forging of this place.<br>
Let yourself sink in, take some time and maybe even listen to lofi while reading this.</p>
<h2 id="setting-first">Setting first</h2>
<p>A cloudy cold friday comes to an end, you come home from work as its get dark outside. You come home, step into your empty apartment you look into the kitchen seeing a few dishes that need cleaning.</p>
<p>You take you shoes off, put down you backpack while going over the day in your head vibing to instrumental music blasting out the headphones.</p>
<h2 id="here-it-comes">Here it comes</h2>
<p>Right I should take them off or at least turn down the volume&hellip; As I take them off, you become more aware off your surroundings. Silence I walk towards the living room in total darkness as a lightning strike lights up the room, making all the shadow monsters go away.</p>
<p>I shiver as the darkness returns with all its monsters, heavy rain hits the windows I turn on the light look a round the room seeing my desk full with shit almost not useable. I go to sofa and sit on it thinking about what I wanna do, as you just recently learned a lot about devops even though you work as a devops engineer.</p>
<p>You just never learn enough, I keep thinking as I had an idea 6 months ago about a domain a vision for a place to be. A place where a community could form or just a place for people to stop by watching YouTube while not being tracked or heck even use TikTok thanks to ProxiTok.</p>
<p>I take open up the laptop, mindlessly you type in the password as it unlocks you feel a feeling coming to your mind. I I I don&rsquo;t know what do I wanted to do? Right watch the data streams flowing through my cluster knowing I do something good in this cruel world. As I sit there staring at the grafana dashboard, a domain name comes to my mind <code>TheKitty.zone</code></p>
<h2 id="the-bathroom">The bathroom</h2>
<p>I let the name roam through my mind as I feel the urge to drink water. I get up walking to the bath room to drink tap water full on knowing that there is a mirror waiting to attack me with my monsters, as I enter the bath room a cold feeling over comes me.</p>
<p>You try not to give the mirror a look any attention at all, you just wanna get a few sips of water. Water flows in the sink I form a vessel with my hands, let it fill with water and then bring it to my mouth so I can drink the water. The cold water bites my throat as I drink it, you feel right at home with these little bites Then, then you accidentally look up right in the mirror. A shock fills me as the body I posses look right at me in the mirror, right and left you see the others.</p>
<h2 id="the-others">The others</h2>
<p>Not really bodies, I can only feel them. One the girl I want to be the other the selfless mind wanting nothing but making others feel good. The host, a boy body housing the wrong minds.</p>
<h2 id="back-to-the-afternoon">Back to the afternoon</h2>
<p>I enter a staring battle, with every second passing inducing more and more pain until sadness fills me, her. I go back into the living room I grab the laptop, ready to make a bad decision in hindsight. So you make the decision that is gonna destroy you for the following days, something so painful you don&rsquo;t know why I did it in the first place. Until the you feel the pain, you go on buying the a for mentioned domain and begin to setup external dns with it while migrating all services to it.</p>
<p>60 Minutes later the pain sets in from the bad decision&hellip; Fuck I really really want him back.
The rain still going on while the thunderstorm seemed to have stopped So I lay there on the sofa crying after him</p>
<p>What do you do, what do you think<br>
Nothing is forever but be sure to know what you need<br>
As it can be over in seconds like this insight view into my head</p>
<h2 id="the-end">The End</h2> ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>About page</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/about-page/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/about-page/</guid><description>&lt;p>Now with a &lt;a href="https://thekitty.zone/about/">about page&lt;/a>, it contains some really cool info you will like it.&lt;br>
Yaay hihihihhi&amp;hellip; Go read!&lt;/p></description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Now with a <a href="https://thekitty.zone/about/">about page</a>, it contains some really cool info you will like it.<br>
Yaay hihihihhi&hellip; Go read!</p>
<p>Wait you are still here..??!!</p> ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>19427539-eb19-46ba-a8ea-4b439a206a87</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/19427539-eb19-46ba-a8ea-4b439a206a87/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 11:33:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/19427539-eb19-46ba-a8ea-4b439a206a87/</guid><description>Nothing that happens is ever forgotten, even if you can&amp;rsquo;t remember it.
Theres more to it than it meets the eye</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Nothing that happens is ever forgotten, even if you can&rsquo;t remember it.</p>
<p>Theres more to it than it meets the eye</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 00:05:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/posts/hello-world/</guid><description>Ah uh hai there!
I didn&amp;rsquo;t notice you coming here, may you want take alook around here?
I know it looks kinda empty but trust me it will getmore comfy over time&amp;hellip;</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Ah uh hai there!<br>
I didn&rsquo;t notice you coming here, may you want take alook around here?</p>
<p>I know it looks kinda empty but trust me it will getmore comfy over time&hellip;</p>
<p>
<img class="enclosure" src="/images/hand-wave-anime.gif" alt="haii"  />
</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>About the project</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/about/</guid><description>The kitty zone is a place where you can feel safe, be yourself and not worry about big tech watching or tracking you.
You may ask why this name?
Well, I wanted it to be more then just a Y instance of Z project hence I came up with this name/domain.
Also I feel the need to express myself on the internet while not being like everyone else just using social media, instead I also want to give back to people who don&amp;rsquo;t want to jump through all the hoops to host all kind of services.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>The kitty zone is a place where you can feel safe, be yourself and not worry about big tech watching or tracking you.<br>
You may ask why this name?<br>
Well, I wanted it to be more then just a Y instance of Z project hence I came up with this name/domain.</p>
<p>Also I feel the need to express myself on the internet while not being like everyone else just using social media, instead I also want to give back to people who don&rsquo;t want to jump through all the hoops to host all kind of services.</p>
<h2 id="about-me">About me</h2>
<p>I&rsquo;m just someone that is interested in DevOps and Software Engineering.<br>
I go by 89Q12/Zozo depending on where you see me online.<br>
I my opinion social media is really really unproductive and to say the least its plain dangerous but who has their own homepage right? right? :&gt;)</p>
<p>I love tinkering with Terraform, Ansible and Kubernetes k3s to be specific :) So I always try to deliver the experience while not taking anything not even more data then required, which leads quite good to the policy part.</p>
<h2 id="polices">Polices</h2>
<p>Logging:<br>
What gets logged across all services:</p>
<ul>
<li>Request timestamp</li>
<li>Accessed services:
<ul>
<li>Service namespace</li>
<li>Service name</li>
<li>Service port</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Response timestamp</li>
<li>Status code</li>
</ul>
<p>That&rsquo;s it! I really don&rsquo;t need more to get a good understanding of what is going on and what services are used much, which not so much and which are unhealthy.</p>
<p>You might ask yourself but can&rsquo;t she correlate requests to users?<br>
No, I can&rsquo;t since these log lines I get from traefik don&rsquo;t contain any Personal indetifyable information about the client.<br>
You don&rsquo;t trust me? Good!<br>
You can just visit this repository <a href="https://github.com/Thekitty-zone/k3s-infra/blob/d41397556d7be647ffdc8e6696a3f22e932d8c4d/deployments/traefik/traefik.yaml#L30">here</a> and check the traefik deployment file youself.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Donate to The Kitty Zone</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/donate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/donate/</guid><description>Why donate? Well the infrastructure behind this project is quite expensive because I try to deliver a pleasing experience to you the user!
A short explanation of the infrastructure Hosters Netcup(One vps providing the mail server and acts as the S3 gateway) Hetzner(Houses 12 servers that run Kubernetes and Ceph) Server Hetzner: Kubernetes cluster: Nodes: 3x cx41 in Falkenstein, 4 cores with 16GB of ram and 180GB local SSD storage 3x cx41 in Nuremberg, 4 cores with 16GB of ram and 180GB local SSD storage 3x cx41 in Helsinki, 4 cores with 16GB of ram and 180GB local SSD storage Controlplanes: 1x cx21 in Falkenstein, 1 core with 4GB of ram and 40GB local SSD storage 1x cx21 in Nuremberg, 1 core with 4GB of ram and 40GB local SSD storage 1x cx21 in Helsinki, 1 core with 4GB of ram and 40GB local SSD storage Ceph cluster: 2x root server with 8 cores, 64GB of ram and 8TB storage in Falkenstein 1x root server with 8 cores, 64GB of ram and 1.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <h2 id="why-donate">Why donate?</h2>
<p>Well the infrastructure behind this project is quite expensive because I try to deliver a pleasing experience to you the user!</p>
<h2 id="a-short-explanation-of-the-infrastructure">A short explanation of the infrastructure</h2>
<h2 id="hosters">Hosters</h2>
<ul>
<li>Netcup(One vps providing the mail server and acts as the S3 gateway)</li>
<li>Hetzner(Houses 12 servers that run Kubernetes and Ceph)</li>
</ul>
<h2 id="server">Server</h2>
<h1 id="hetzner">Hetzner:</h1>
<ul>
<li>Kubernetes cluster:
<ul>
<li>Nodes:
<ul>
<li>3x cx41 in Falkenstein, 4 cores with 16GB of ram and 180GB local SSD storage</li>
<li>3x cx41 in Nuremberg, 4 cores with 16GB of ram and 180GB local SSD storage</li>
<li>3x cx41 in Helsinki, 4 cores with 16GB of ram and 180GB local SSD storage</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Controlplanes:
<ul>
<li>1x cx21 in Falkenstein, 1 core with 4GB of ram and 40GB local SSD storage</li>
<li>1x cx21 in Nuremberg, 1 core with 4GB of ram and 40GB local SSD storage</li>
<li>1x cx21 in Helsinki, 1 core with 4GB of ram and 40GB local SSD storage</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>Ceph cluster:
<ul>
<li>2x root server with 8 cores, 64GB of ram and 8TB storage in Falkenstein</li>
<li>1x root server with 8 cores, 64GB of ram and 1.7TB SSD storage</li>
</ul>
</li>
</ul>
<h1 id="netcup">Netcup</h1>
<ul>
<li>1x root server with 6 cores, 32GB of ram and 800GB SSD storage</li>
</ul>
<p>This all has a cost of <strong>326€</strong> per month!<br>
Currently I pay all this myself and that is fine, its within my monthly &lsquo;play money&rsquo; budget.</p>
<h2 id="where-to-donate">Where to donate</h2>
<h1 id="cryptocurrencies">Cryptocurrencies:</h1>
<ul>
<li>
<p>Monero:</p>
<ul>
<li><a href="monero:43GsD8kyArZPZdCN9N9NLAS4TmnGEf29RMTXWLQD3DCyb5Ad4hqNrEfQyWdSXbaNU4Sq5WQ2UfSspeNVDNc5C6uzPqsfBCR%22%3E43GsD8kyArZPZdCN9N9NLAS4TmnGEf29RMTXWLQD3DCyb5Ad4hqNrEfQyWdSXbaNU4Sq5WQ2UfSspeNVDNc5C6uzPqsfBCR">43GsD8kyArZPZdCN9N9NLAS4TmnGEf29RMTXWLQD3DCyb5Ad4hqNrEfQyWdSXbaNU4Sq5WQ2UfSspeNVDNc5C6uzPqsfBCR&quot;&gt;43GsD8kyArZPZdCN9N9NLAS4TmnGEf29RMTXWLQD3DCyb5Ad4hqNrEfQyWdSXbaNU4Sq5WQ2UfSspeNVDNc5C6uzPqsfBCR</a></li>
</ul>
</li>
<li>
<p>PIVX: DCgg7RQ7tgG1HjYYq1uE4L6Ax5ErM9A9fk</p>
</li>
</ul>
<p>more coming soon&hellip;</p>
<h1 id="other-ways">Other ways:</h1>
<p><a href="https://github.com/sponsors/89Q12">Github sponsers</a></p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Librarian</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/lbry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/lbry/</guid><description>Sick of YouTube but hate Odyssee, well with Librarian you can use Lbry tracking free. Librarian is a privacy focused frontend for Odyssee aka Lbry.
As always nothing gets logged except that someone accessed the service.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Sick of YouTube but hate Odyssee, well with <a href="https://codeberg.org/librarian/librarian">Librarian</a> you can use Lbry tracking free. Librarian is a privacy focused frontend for Odyssee aka Lbry.</p>
<p>As always nothing gets logged except that <em>someone</em> accessed the service.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Libreddit</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/libreddit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/libreddit/</guid><description>Perhaps you wanna reddit the kitty zone, Libreddit is privacy focused frontend for reddit. Unlike teddit it has a newer feeling interfaces and is written in Rust.
It use dark theme by default and uses hls for videos meaning they are proxied thorugh my servers.
NFSW is also visible by default.
As always nothing gets logged except that someone accessed the service.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Perhaps you wanna reddit the kitty zone, <a href="https://github.com/libreddit/libreddit">Libreddit</a> is privacy focused frontend for reddit. Unlike teddit it has a newer feeling interfaces and is written in Rust.<br>
It use dark theme by default and uses hls for videos meaning they are proxied thorugh my servers.<br>
NFSW is also visible by default.</p>
<p>As always nothing gets logged except that <em>someone</em> accessed the service.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>My PIVX Wallet</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/mpw/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/mpw/</guid><description>A portable wallet for the PIVX currency.
Why? Well diversity in the instances of MyPIVXWallet is great right? Right</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>A portable <a href="https://github.com/PIVX-Labs/MyPIVXWallet">wallet</a> for the PIVX currency.<br>
Why? Well diversity in the instances of MyPIVXWallet is great right? Right</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>ProxiTok</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/proxitok/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/proxitok/</guid><description>Sick of people sending you TikTok links? ProxiTok is a privacy focused frontend for TikTok making it easy to view a video without being tracked but we all know answering the person with &amp;ldquo;Mhh yeah&amp;rdquo; is the right call.
As always nothing gets logged except that someone accessed the service.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Sick of people sending you TikTok links? <a href="https://github.com/pablouser1/ProxiTok">ProxiTok</a> is a privacy focused frontend for TikTok making it easy to view a video without being tracked but we all know answering the person with &ldquo;Mhh yeah&rdquo; is the right call.</p>
<p>As always nothing gets logged except that <em>someone</em> accessed the service.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Rimgo</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/rimgo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/rimgo/</guid><description>View all the pics in the kitty zone, Rimgo is a privacy focused frontend for Imgur.
As always nothing gets logged except that someone accessed the service.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>View all the pics in the kitty zone, <a href="https://codeberg.org/video-prize-ranch/rimgo">Rimgo</a> is a privacy focused frontend for Imgur.</p>
<p>As always nothing gets logged except that <em>someone</em> accessed the service.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item><item><title>Search the kitty zone</title><link>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/searx/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.thekitty.zone/services/searx/</guid><description>Search the kitty zone, powered by Searx.
Configured with relativ speed in mind while also giving accurate results and autocomplete turned on by default.
POST is used as opossed to GET for improved privacy.
As always nothing gets logged except that someone accessed the service.</description><content:encoded><![CDATA[ <p>Search the kitty zone, powered by <a href="https://github.com/searxng/searxng">Searx</a>.<br>
Configured with relativ speed in mind while also giving accurate results and autocomplete turned on by default.<br>
POST is used as opossed to GET for improved privacy.</p>
<p>As always nothing gets logged except that <em>someone</em> accessed the service.</p>
 ]]></content:encoded></item></channel></rss>